cherrydale.com 2013-05-24

# Cherrydale Farms Fundraising - School Fundraiser, School Fundraising Ideas and More

Privacy Policy concerning Data collected online.

At Cherry Brothers LLC, we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and the users of our Site, and this Privacy Policy Statement sets our policy on the gathering and use of information on this Site.

There may be links from this Site to other web sites but please note that this Privacy Statement applies only to this Site and not to web sites of other companies or organizations to which this Site is linked.

Although you are not required to register to access this Site, you may be asked to provide us with personal information when you visit certain sections of the Site, or to download software from this site.

How does Cherry Brothers LLC use information gathered about its online visitors?  
Any consumer information gathered on this Site may be used for aggregate research, promotional purposes and/or for future site development. In particular we may use information gathered about you for the following purposes: to send you or, where appropriate, your organization, information about us and promotional material about our products together with details of any offers we may have available from time to time; to monitor interest in our range of products and to assist us to tailor the content of our Site to your needs by collecting information about your preferences through tracking patterns of page views on this site; and to create a profile relating to you in order to show you the content that might be of interest to you and to display the content according to your preferences.

**Disclosure of Information**  
Cherry Brothers LLC will not disclose personal identifiable information that you provide on this Site to any third parties other than to an Cherry Brothers LLC employee except:  
i) in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy statement, or  
ii) to comply with valid legal requirements such as law, regulation, warrant, subpoena or court order.

**Cookies**  
Cherry Brothers LLC, in common with many web site operators, may use standard technology called cookies on this Site. Cookies are small data files that are downloaded onto your computer when you visit a particular web site. You can disable cookies by turning them off in your browser, however, some areas of this Site may not function properly if you do so.

**Security**  
This Site incorporates appropriate safeguards using industry standard technology to heighten the security, accuracy and privacy of any personal information we have collected and we have put in place reasonable precautions to protect information from loss and misuse. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as required.

**Policy Change**  
If we alter our privacy policy, any changes will be posted on this page of our Site so that you are always informed of the information we collect about you, how we use it and the circumstances under which we may disclose it. Please check back from time to time to ensure you are aware of our current privacy policy. We appreciate your interest and hope that you enjoy visiting the Site.

**Contact Details** If at any time you wish to contact Cherry Brothers LLC with any question or complaint or to exercise any of the rights set out in this privacy policy statement, you may do so by contacting Cherry Brothers LLC by either of the methods set out below:

E-mail us at [info@cherrydale.com](mailto:info@cherrydale.com) or Click here to visit our online "contact us" form!
